Hey guys, before diving into the topics and the practical section, we need to install multiple
things like a few lab environment and a few applications that will be helpful for performing
our programming activities. So, the first one that was virtual box. So, we all know why
we are installing virtual box in the environment. So, this will be creating a, so this
is used to create a sandbox environment. We can test anything using the virtual machines
we can, we can download it and we can install it and we can install some of the machine
and we can test it out. So, you will understand why we are going to do. So, my suggestion
will be install the virtual machine for some like a 7 version, 7.1.12. So, here I was
using this because the latest version we are getting some errors. So, you can find stone
pine on pine. You can install this. So, let us, I have already downloaded the application
before, a stone pine on pine for this, the one. So, I will be giving, I will be giving
the link to, link in the video resource or not a problem. You can download it, the windows
host if you are a Mac install or you can go ahead everything. So, also download the extension
pack of the application. So, we need both of the things. So, once you have successfully
downloaded just install the virtual machine. So, it is a simple, you need to give next
next, nothing special apart from that. Let us wait for some time and it will continue
the installation. So, now the installation has been successful and let us install the extension
also install. So, you need to double the extension, that is all nothing special in this.
So, yeah, I hope the extension is also installed and yeah, the extension is also installed
and we are good with that. So, we are working on multiple offensive tools, multiple, we
are handling multiple malware. So, the primary goal is to our malware. If we are running
our malware in the primary machine. So, this will impact your primary machine side. So,
instead of running the malware on the primary machine, we are creating a test environment,
they are a team environment and we are running the malware and hacking machine inside
the test environment. So, this is like a sandbox. So, we just created a small sandbox
and we are putting everything inside the sandbox and we are running into that. So, many
one ask why we need a sandbox. So, if you want to test, if you want to blast a nuclear
weapon or something, so what the engineers will do? They will dig into the sand and they
will be putting inside the sand and they will be close it off and they will be blast
it right. So, that is the scenario. So, we are going to do here.
So, let us hop off from here and we will continue our discussion next video. I hope everyone
I installed the environment, ok. So, see you guys, bye bye.